Before you go, the post-modern
society from a stoicistisc perspective,
475 pages, hand in on Monday.
I've bloody well...
Do you recognize yourself? You are not
alone. വിക്കിപീഡിയ is Swedens sixth most
visited page, so chances are pretty high
that your students go there to find facts
and information, just there. Perhaps even
you as educator do that?
But how can you know whether the articles
on വിക്കിപീഡിയ are reliable or not?
I'll give you three tips. The tips, they are
So, Ta and Hi.
So, it is sources. They exists at the
bottom of the വിക്കിപീഡിയ articles.
Look at how many it is and if you think they are good sources.
Please do click through on
the source to see where you end up.
Second is Ta, this means Talk. For
each article, there is a tab, go in and see
what people are talking about. Do they
even talk about anything? If they are, it is
usually about content and structure. If
there is a discussion about the article, it
usually makes the article better. It shows
many have been in the article and studied
and considered what is in the article and
how it should look like.
Last is Hi, History. That is also a tab.
Check how many have added information
and removed  information. The more
contributers and people partaking in
discussions, the better.
It makes article a lot more credible.
So it is three simple things, So, Ta and Hi.
Please take a look on this together with your
students in order to evaluate an article's
credibility on വിക്കിപീഡിയ.
On വിക്കിമീഡിയ സ്വീഡൻ, we are working
with the education programme വിക്കിപീഡിയ
in Education. Please let us know if you
are curious, thoughtful or maybe skeptical?
We want to hear from you.
What we do, is to make വിക്കിപീഡിയ
accessible, useful and understandable.
We would really like to hear from you.
വിക്കിപീഡിയ in Education
Are you fed up with വിക്കിപീഡിയ?
Can you not get enough of വിക്കിപീഡിയ?
Contact us on
utbildning@wikimedia.se